import { Question } from '@/src/types/questions'

const family: Question[] = [
  {
    "question": "Which kanji represents \"otousan\"?",
    "options": [
      "お父さん",
      "父",
      "奥さん",
      "兄弟"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "父"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which kanji represents \"oniisan\"?",
    "options": [
      "父",
      "お兄さん",
      "奥さん",
      "兄"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "兄"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does \"姉\" mean?",
    "options": [
      "older sister",
      "siblings",
      "husband",
      "family"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "older sister"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"younger brother\"?",
    "options": [
      "otouto",
      "tsuma",
      "okusan",
      "ane"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "otouto"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does 'お姉さん' mean?",
    "options": [
      "older sister",
      "father",
      "wife",
      "mother"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "older sister"
  },


  {
    "question": "Which Japanese word corresponds to 'goshujin'?",
    "options": [
      "ご主人",
      "父",
      "奥さん",
      "お父さん"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ご主人"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does \"父\" mean?",
    "options": [
      "father",
      "older brother",
      "sisters",
      "younger sister"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "father"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"otousan\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "おとうさん",
      "おにいさん",
      "あね",
      "ともだち"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "おとうさん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"older sister\"?",
    "options": [
      "ane",
      "oniisan",
      "chichi",
      "shimai"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ane"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"kodomo\"?",
    "options": [
      "child",
      "younger sister",
      "wife",
      "older sister"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "child"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does \"弟\" mean?",
    "options": [
      "younger brother",
      "older sister",
      "family",
      "wife"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "younger brother"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"imootosan\"?",
    "options": [
      "younger sister",
      "older brother",
      "father",
      "mother"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "younger sister"
  },


  {
    "question": "Which kanji corresponds to 'kyoudai'?",
    "options": ["兄弟", "姉妹", "父", "母"],
    "correctAnswer": "兄弟"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which word (with kanji) corresponds to \"oneesan\"?",
    "options": [
      "お姉さん",
      "ご家族",
      "ご兄弟",
      "友達"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "お姉さん"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which kanji corresponds to 'ane'?",
    "options": ["姉", "妹", "母", "友"],
    "correctAnswer": "姉"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write 'gokazoku' in Hiragana?",
    "options": ["ごかぞく", "いもうとさん", "こども", "おとうと"],
    "correctAnswer": "ごかぞく"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write 'goshujin' in Hiragana?",
    "options": ["ごしゅじん", "しまい", "おとうとさん", "おねえさん"],
    "correctAnswer": "ごしゅじん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"okusan\"?",
    "options": [
      "wife",
      "older brother",
      "younger brother",
      "child"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "wife"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which kanji corresponds to 'imouto'?",
    "options": ["妹", "姉", "母", "友"],
    "correctAnswer": "妹"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which kanji corresponds to 'tomodachi'?",
    "options": ["友達", "姉妹", "母", "父"],
    "correctAnswer": "友達"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which kanji corresponds to 'shimai'?",
    "options": ["姉妹", "兄弟", "母", "父"],
    "correctAnswer": "姉妹"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"older sister\"?",
    "options": [
      "oneesan",
      "kyoudai",
      "gokyoudai",
      "goshujin"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "oneesan"
  },


  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"otoutosan\"?",
    "options": [
      "younger brother",
      "siblings",
      "husband",
      "younger sister"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "younger brother"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"ani\"?",
    "options": [
      "older brother",
      "friend",
      "younger sister",
      "husband"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "older brother"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the word \"弟さん\" mean?",
    "options": [
      "younger brother",
      "father",
      "older brother",
      "wife"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "younger brother"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for 'otoutosan'?",
    "options": [
      "お母さん",
      "主人",
      "ご主人",
      "弟さん",      
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "弟さん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the kanji \"母\" mean?",
    "options": [
      "mother",
      "older brother",
      "father",
      "wife"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "mother"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which kanji corresponds to \"kazoku\"?",
    "options": [
      "家族",
      "主人",
      "奥さん",
      "お母さん"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "家族"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the word \"お兄さん\" mean?",
    "options": [
      "older brother",
      "older sister",
      "siblings",
      "older brother"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "older brother"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"gokyoudai\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "ごきょうだい",
      "おかあさん",
      "ちち",
      "おとうとさん"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ごきょうだい"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does \"奥さん\" mean?",
    "options": [
      "wife",
      "husband",
      "younger brother",
      "siblings"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "wife"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which kanji corresponds to \"gokazoku\"?",
    "options": [
      "ご家族",
      "お母さん",
      "兄弟",
      "弟さん"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ご家族"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which kanji corresponds to \"shujin\"?",
    "options": [
      "主人",
      "兄弟",
      "子供",
      "妹さん"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "主人"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"shimai\"?",
    "options": [
      "sisters",
      "siblings",
      "wife",
      "older brother"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "sisters"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"wife\"?",
    "options": [
      "tsuma",
      "gokyoudai",
      "otouto",
      "goshujin"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "tsuma"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"oneesan\"?",
    "options": [
      "older sister",
      "husband",
      "friend",
      "younger brother"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "older sister"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which kanji corresponds to \"okusan\"?",
    "options": [
      "奥さん",
      "兄弟",
      "弟",
      "ご主人"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "奥さん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"tsuma\"?",
    "options": [
      "wife",
      "husband",
      "older sister",
      "child"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "wife"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which kanji corresponds to \"imootosan\"?",
    "options": [
      "妹さん",
      "ご家族",
      "お母さん",
      "主人"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "妹さん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does \"妹さん\" mean?",
    "options": [
      "younger sister",
      "older sister",
      "older brother",
      "siblings"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "younger sister"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"family\"?",
    "options": [
      "gokazoku",
      "okusan",
      "shujin",
      "oneesan"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "gokazoku"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which kanji corresponds to \"otouto\"?",
    "options": [
      "弟",
      "弟さん",
      "奥さん",
      "母"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "弟"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"father\"?",
    "options": [
      "chichi",
      "ani",
      "gokyoudai",
      "okusan"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "chichi"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"family\"?",
    "options": [
      "kazoku",
      "ani",
      "tsuma",
      "otouto"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "kazoku"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does \"家族\" mean?",
    "options": [
      "family",
      "older sister",
      "mother",
      "wife"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "family"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"ane\"?",
    "options": [
      "older sister",
      "sisters",
      "family",
      "wife"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "older sister"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which kanji corresponds to \"haha\"?",
    "options": [
      "母",
      "兄弟",
      "主人",
      "お姉さん"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "母"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"goshujin\"?",
    "options": [
      "husband",
      "older sister",
      "younger brother",
      "mother"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "husband"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"child\"?",
    "options": [
      "kodomo",
      "goshujin",
      "haha",
      "otousan"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "kodomo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"younger brother\"?",
    "options": [
      "otoutosan",
      "goshujin",
      "chichi",
      "ani"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "otoutosan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which kanji corresponds to \"kyoudai\"?",
    "options": [
      "兄弟",
      "お姉さん",
      "兄",
      "弟"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "兄弟"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"okaasan\"?",
    "options": [
      "mother",
      "younger sister",
      "wife",
      "older sister"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "mother"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"older brother\"?",
    "options": [
      "ani",
      "shujin",
      "otoutosan",
      "okaasan"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ani"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"wife\"?",
    "options": [
      "okusan",
      "shimai",
      "otousan",
      "otouto"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "okusan"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does \"ご主人\" mean?",
    "options": [
      "husband",
      "older brother",
      "siblings",
      "younger brother"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "husband"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"haha\"?",
    "options": [
      "mother",
      "husband",
      "friend",
      "younger brother"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "mother"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"mother\"?",
    "options": [
      "ani",
      "kazoku",
      "otouto",
      "haha"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "okaasan"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"younger sister\"?",
    "options": [
      "chichi",
      "gokyoudai",
      "shimai",
      "imouto"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "imouto"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does \"お母さん\" mean?",
    "options": [
      "father",
      "mother",
      "older brother",
      "child"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "mother"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"mother\"?",
    "options": [
      "haha",
      "gokazoku",
      "gokyoudai",
      "kyoudai"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "haha"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"oniisan\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "おにいさん",
      "しまい",
      "こども",
      "しゅじん"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "おにいさん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does \"姉妹\" mean?",
    "options": [
      "sisters",
      "wife",
      "child",
      "younger brother"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "sisters"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which kanji corresponds to \"ani\"?",
    "options": [
      "兄",
      "妹",
      "お父さん",
      "ご主人"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "兄"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"husband\"?",
    "options": [
      "shujin",
      "gokyoudai",
      "kazoku",
      "haha"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "shujin"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"oneesan\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "おねえさん",
      "はは",
      "きょうだい",
      "ごしゅじん"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "おねえさん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"tomodachi\"?",
    "options": [
      "friend",
      "father",
      "sisters",
      "younger brother"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "friend"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does \"兄弟\" mean?",
    "options": [
      "siblings",
      "older sister",
      "husband",
      "friend"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "siblings"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"gokyoudai\"?",
    "options": [
      "siblings",
      "older sister",
      "family",
      "wife"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "siblings"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"father\"?",
    "options": [
      "otousan",
      "kazoku",
      "ane",
      "okaasan"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "otousan"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"sisters\"?",
    "options": [
      "shimai",
      "imootosan",
      "ani",
      "goshujin"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "shimai"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"siblings\"?",
    "options": [
      "kyoudai",
      "okaasan",
      "kodomo",
      "oneesan"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "kyoudai"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does \"主人\" mean?",
    "options": [
      "husband",
      "older sister",
      "older brother",
      "younger brother"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "husband"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you write \"okaasan\" in Hiragana?",
    "options": [
      "おかあさん",
      "きょうだい",
      "いもうと",
      "はは"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "おかあさん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"husband\"?",
    "options": [
      "goshujin",
      "shimai",
      "oneesan",
      "imouto"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "goshujin"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"kyoudai\"?",
    "options": [
      "siblings",
      "older brother",
      "older sister",
      "family"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "siblings"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"gokazoku\"?",
    "options": [
      "family",
      "friend",
      "older brother",
      "mother"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "family"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does \"友達\" mean?",
    "options": [
      "friend",
      "family",
      "older brother",
      "younger sister"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "friend"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does \"ご兄弟\" mean?",
    "options": [
      "siblings",
      "child",
      "father"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "siblings"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which kanji corresponds to \"chichi\"?",
    "options": [
      "父",
      "姉妹",
      "お父さん",
      "母"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "父"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which kanji corresponds to \"kodomo\"?",
    "options": [
      "子供",
      "姉妹",
      "父",
      "お姉さん"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "子供"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does \"お父さん\" mean?",
    "options": [
      "father",
      "younger sister",
      "mother",
      "younger brother"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "father"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"younger sister\"?",
    "options": [
      "imootosan",
      "kyoudai",
      "chichi",
      "oneesan"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "imootosan"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does \"妻\" mean?",
    "options": [
      "wife",
      "mother",
      "older sister",
      "younger brother"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "wife"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does \"子供\" mean?",
    "options": [
      "child",
      "wife",
      "husband",
      "older sister"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "child"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"chichi\"?",
    "options": [
      "father",
      "family",
      "friend",
      "sisters"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "father"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"otouto\"?",
    "options": [
      "younger brother",
      "father",
      "younger sister",
      "husband"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "younger brother"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"imouto\"?",
    "options": [
      "younger sister",
      "friend",
      "older brother",
      "father"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "younger sister"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does \"兄\" mean?",
    "options": [
      "older brother",
      "siblings",
      "family"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "older brother"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"siblings\"?",
    "options": [
      "gokyoudai",
      "ani",
      "imootosan",
      "otousan"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "gokyoudai"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"oniisan\"?",
    "options": [
      "older brother",
      "mother",
      "sisters",
      "younger brother"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "older brother"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"friend\"?",
    "options": [
      "tomodachi",
      "okaasan",
      "otoutosan",
      "otousan"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "tomodachi"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"shujin\"?",
    "options": [
      "husband",
      "friend",
      "siblings",
      "wife"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "husband"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which kanji corresponds to \"okaasan\"?",
    "options": [
      "お母さん",
      "兄",
      "兄弟",
      "ご家族"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "お母さん"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does \"ご家族\" mean?",
    "options": [
      "family",
      "friend",
      "younger brother",
      "mother"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "family"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"kazoku\"?",
    "options": [
      "family",
      "younger sister",
      "siblings",
      "older sister"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "family"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which kanji corresponds to \"tsuma\"?",
    "options": [
      "妻",
      "妹",
      "ご家族",
      "ご主人"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "妻"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the meaning of \"otousan\"?",
    "options": [
      "father",
      "wife",
      "younger sister",
      "older brother"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "father"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Japanese word for \"older brother\"?",
    "options": [
      "oniisan",
      "goshujin",
      "gokyoudai",
      "tomodachi"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "oniisan"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does \"妹\" mean?",
    "options": [
      "younger sister",
      "older sister",
      "mother",
      "wife"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "younger sister"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which kanji corresponds to \"ane\"?",
    "options": [
      "姉",
      "妻",
      "家族",
      "兄"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "姉"
  }
];

export default family;
